<xml version="1.0">
  <!--Generated by ElementTree in webScraper.py at 2013-02-20 22:23:50.783047-->
  <Schedule>
<Event>
<description>"Join us as we preview episodes V - VIII of Chop Socky Boom: A Misfortunate Web Comedy. Cast members Jen Page, Jay Irwin, Brandon Ryan, Andrew McMasters and show creators Darlene Sellers and Heath Ward will be on hand to talk about the making of the series as well as talk about real life stories on making indie films in Seattle. Fans of films like Kung Fu Hustle and Kung Pow! Enter the Fist will certainly be entertained as will anyone else who just enjoys good comedy!"</description> 
<end>"3/4/2013 3:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"2AB"</location>
 <name>"CHOP SOCKY BOOM"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
        <description>"&quot;Liberator&quot; is an independent short film starring Lou Ferrigno (The Incredible Hulk) as a washed-up, disgraced ex-superhero trying to get his life back on the rails. Rounding out the ubergeek all-star cast is Peta Wilson (La Femme Nikita), Michael Dorn (Star Trek TNG), Don 'The Dragon' Wilson' (Bloodfist) and Ed Asner (Up.) Liberator was financed both out of pocket and via a successful Kickstarter campaign, in which $26K was raised. But still, how could we possibly hope to compete with the 9-figure budgets of today's superhero movies with the budget of a Toyota? By being damn crafty and keeping true to what our fellow geeks really want in a movie! Check out the beginning of a new Sci Fi franchise!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"2AB"</location>
 <name>"LIBERATOR: STARTING A NEW SUPERHERO FRANCHISE FOR 11 BUCKS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Straight Outta Comicon is fan comedy by professional geeks. Disheartened with the traditional stand-up comedy scene, travelling comics Matt McInnis and Matt Keck joined forces to set aside &quot;club comedy&quot; and &quot;club material&quot; to bring their true love, nerd comedy, to cons and like-minded fans across the country. Straight Outta Comicon is a two man stand-up comedy and variety show that has been welcomed by stages, fans and conventions far and wide. Straight Outta Comicon includes stand-up comedy, music, sketch work, improv, audience participation, and a staggering level of fandom. "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"2AB"</location>
 <name>"STRAIGHT OUTTA COMICON" </name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Do you love Star Wars AND the color pink? Spend equal amounts of time shopping for clothes AND comics? There's no shame in being geeky and feminine! Join panelists Bonnie Burton (author of The Star Wars Craft Book), Kristina Horner (YouTube vlogger &quot;italktosnakes&quot;), Molly McIsaac (geek fashion blogger and cosplayer), and Tara Theoharis (geek lifestyle blogger at Geekyhostess.com) as they celebrate the people and things that make being geeky and feminine fantastic! Men and women are welcome to participate in this lively discussion on what it means to be a geeky woman in the 21st Century."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"2AB"</location>
 <name>"I CAN BE A GEEK AND FEMININE"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"America's Fighting Dinosaur is a faux-documentary series that explores the life and military career of Pvt. &quot;Little&quot; Sammy Vogel, a 7 ton, 40 foot long Army infantryman and T-Rex who fought for the Allies in WWII. Using photos, archive footage, letters and interviews with veterans and soldiers who served by his side, the series sheds some light on how America's biggest soldier managed to go unheard of for so long. We'll be premiering segments from the series and doing a Q&amp;A with writer/director Steve Snoey, producer Lacey Leavitt, cinematographer Nathan Miller and composer Eric Nielson."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"2AB"</location>
 <name>"AMERICA'S FIGHTING DINOSAUR"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Karaoke Hero makes a return to the Emerald City Comicon courtesy of Absolute Karaoke. Join host Josh Baron as he brings you all the fun. Part singing contest, part costume contest, Karaoke Hero is all fun! Will you bear witness to a Silver Surfer singing &quot;Space Oddity&quot;? Or perhaps you will see The Punisher singing &quot;Sound Of Madness&quot;. Anything is possible! No costume? No worries. Everyone is welcome to come sing. Heck, you don't even have to be a great singer! You just need the desire to have fun!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 12:00AM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"2AB"</location>
 <name>"KARAOKE HERO"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 8:15PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"VP of Publishing, Jim Kuhoric, will lead a panel discussing Avatar's big events slated for 2013, including why this year's C-Day will be bigger than ever. With Garth Ennis returning to Crossed: Badlands in March, we will dive into details on the upcoming Crossed live-action webisodes. What writers are slated to take a stab at the Crossed universe this year? Kieron Gillen's new ongoing WWII revisionist series, Uber, launches in April - what is it all about? What does Christos Gage's Absolution sequel have in store for this summer? What is the next big project for Alan Moore, Garth Ennis, Si Spurrier? Join the panel and see what info will be revealed. It will be a bloody good time. "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 3:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"3AB"</location>
 <name>"AVATAR PRESS: BRINGING YOU THE BLOODY BEST IN 2013"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Ever wonder how some of your favorite creators broke in to comics, or were curious how some up-and-comers get to be “up-and-comers”? Join some of Archaia’s creators for a lively discussion of how they got their first break in comics, and to hear their advice of how you can, too! Panelists include Chandra Free (The God Machine, Fraggle Rock), Andrew E.C. Gaska (Space: 1999: Afterchock and Awe, Conspiracy of the Planet of the Apes), Royden Lepp (Rust), David Marquez (Syndrome, All-New X-Men), Yehudi Mercado (Pantalones, TX), David Petersen (Mouse Guard), and Charles Soule (Strange Attractors)."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"3AB"</location>
 <name>"ARCHAIA PRESENTS: HOW I BROKE INTO COMICS (AND HOW YOU CAN TOO!)"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Hugo Award winning writer Morgan Gendel talks about &quot;The Inner Light&quot;, the #1 fan favorite episode of Star Trek: The Next Generation. Accompanied by clips from the episode, Morgan will talk about how he got the idea for &quot;The Inner Light&quot; as well as discuss how he developed the episode with the young ST:TNG producers who are now household names to Trek fans. Subjects will include his post-TNG work as the writer-producer of more than 200 episodes of primetime TV plus a sneak preview of his current movie project with Stan Lee."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"3AB"</location>
 <name>"JOURNEY TO THE INNER LIGHT"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"The Bushwick Book Club Seattle presents original music inspired by Neil Gaiman's &quot;The Sandman&quot;. We will have a group of songwriters perform their original creations inspired by The Sandman. And join us for our full set Saturday night at the Crocodile!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"3AB"</location>
 <name>"THE BUSHWICK BOOK CLUB - SEATTLE"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Jeff Parker, writer of fan-favorite comics like Red She-Hulk and Agents of Atlas, sits down with David Brothers to have a frank and funny conversation about what working on comics is really like, where inspiration actually comes from, and why if you want to be a pro you need to stop being a fan. Do you have preconceptions of what the comics industry is like? Come through and watch this tag team destroy them with jokes, opinions, and hard facts."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"3AB"</location>
 <name>"PARKER / BROTHERS: LIFE IN AND AROUND COMICS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join the creators of Job Hunters, (Forest Gibson, Liz Leo, Kristina Horner, Tara Theoharis), the Seattle-based dystopian web series for a screening and Q&amp;A. There may even be some surprises... (check us out at www.watchjobhunters.com!) "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 8:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"3AB"</location>
 <name>"JOB HUNTERS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 8:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join host Blair Butler (Attack of the Show) as she talks to legendary comic writer Chris Claremont! Subjects are sure to include his unparalleled run of 17 years on &quot;The Uncanny X-Men&quot; and it's many spin off titles, his work with George Lucas on &quot;Chronicles of the Shadow War&quot; (which continued the story of Elora Danan from the movie &quot;Willow&quot;) as well as his creator owned work, &quot;Sovereign Seven&quot;, which was published by DC Comics in the mid 90's."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 3:35PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"EMERALD"</location>
 <name>"ECCC SPOTLIGHT LOUNGE PRESENTS: SECRET ORIGINS WITH CHRIS CLAREMONT"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 2:40PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"The man who is the co-creator of The Punisher and Firestorm, he's also one of the men responsible for the classic &quot;Death of Gwen Stacy&quot; storyline. As if that weren't enough, he's also the writer for the first major, modern-day intercompany crossover, &quot;Superman vs. the Amazing Spider-Man&quot;. If you don't know his name, it's Gerry Conway! Come spend an hour as Blair Butler (writer, &quot;Heart&quot;) goes one on one with an industry legend! "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:35PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"EMERALD"</location>
 <name>"ECCC SPOTLIGHT LOUNGE PRESENTS: SECRET ORIGINS WITH GERRY CONWAY"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:40PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join us as we talk with Monkeybrain Comics Chris Roberson! Chris will talk about his work as a novelist (Clockwork Storybook, Here, There &amp; Everywhere), his subsequent work at DC Comics (iZombie, Superman, Cinderella) and his pioneering work in the field of self publishing."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:35PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"EMERALD"</location>
 <name>"ECCC SPOTLIGHT LOUNGE PRESENTS: SECRET ORIGINS WITH CHRIS ROBERSON"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:40PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Simon Bisley first gained prominence with his work in 2000 AD, but it was his work on DC Comics Lobo that propelled Simon Bisley into the realm of super star. Blair Butler (G4's X-Play) talks to the man, the myth and the legend that is Simon Bisley!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:35PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"EMERALD"</location>
 <name>"ECCC SPOTLIGHT LOUNGE PRESENTS: SECRET ORIGINS WITH SIMON BISLEY"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:40PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"The world-renowned artist Coop joins us for an hour to talk about his more than two decades long career creating subversive, vice-centric images. His smoking devils, big beautiful women, amped-up hotrods, and berserk monsters have become counter culture icons. A  pioneer of the Lowbrow art movement, Coop has attained celebrity status in the gig poster, Kustom Kulture, and tattoo communities. Sure to be a fascinating hour!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:35PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"EMERALD"</location>
 <name>"ECCC SPOTLIGHT LOUNGE PRESENTS: SECRET ORIGINS WITH COOP!"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:40PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Final Fantasy: The Improvised Adventures tells an improvised tale in the style of the Final Fantasy video games. Knights, wizards, thieves and scholars band together in a completely impromptu tale of swords and sorcery that will culminate in an epic struggle for the fate of the world. The series of over a dozen video games are lovingly riffed upon in this parody tribute. The experienced ensemble of actors, working with little more than their wits and imaginations will take ideas from the audience, and turn them into a sidesplitting production that will be enjoyed by both veterans of the series and complete strangers alike."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 3:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"GAMING"</location>
 <name>"FINAL FANTASY: THE IMPROVISED ADVENTURES"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"The hysterical Paul and Storm lead a panel discussion about their awesome new project LearningTown, where the comedy music duo try to save a kid’s show from the threat of cancellation, greedy exes, and ironic hipsters. They will be joined by Learning Town head writer Josh Cagan. Share your love for nerdy music videos, puppets catching on fire, and get the behind the scenes story from the stars of LearningTown! LearningTown airs Tuesdays on Felicia Day’s popular YouTube channel, Geek &amp; Sundry. "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"GAMING"</location>
 <name>"PAUL AND STORM WELCOME YOU TO LEARNINGTOWN"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"An interpretive dance extravaganza!!! ...or maybe this will be the Extra Credits crew talking game design, development and what more we can do with games. I guess you'll just have to show up to find out."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"GAMING"</location>
 <name>"EXTRA CREDITS PANEL"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Costume Designer Yaya Han talks about simple but effective construction techniques that can elevate your costumes to the next level! From shopping for materials smartly to putting the right finishing touches on your costumes, this is a panel for beginners and advanced costume crafters alike. Come join Yaya for great tips in the areas of sewing, wig styling, prop making and more."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"GAMING"</location>
 <name>"COSPLAY CONSTRUCTION ESSENTIALS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"In an increasingly digitized world, it can be hard to remember that we're not as lean and muscled as our online avatars suggest. Trade in virtual fitness for the real thing with today's panel from Geek and Gamer Fitness! Join Geek and Gamer Fitness owner, Jason Heilpern, as he takes you through the first steps on your way to making your &quot;real&quot; self look as good as your &quot;virtual&quot; self. You can't lose weight, gain muscle, and develop stamina at the click of a mouse alone.  Learn how to level up your life and become even stronger then your online avatar in this fitness panel made for geeks, by geeks!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"GAMING"</location>
 <name>"HOW TO BECOME AS FIT AS YOUR AVATAR - LESSONS FROM GEEK AND GAMER FITNESS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Are you an aspiring comic book writer or artist? Then we've got the panel for you! Join BOOM! Studios Editor-in-Chief Matt Gagnon and other comic book professionals as they give you practical advice on how to make your comic book dreams come true."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 3:25PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"BREAKING INTO COMICS THE BOOM! STUDIOS WAY"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 2:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"&quot;Doctor Who&quot; is the world's most successful science fiction television series. Debuting on the BBC in 1963, it ran for twenty-six years. In 2005, it was revived and became the worldwide phenomenon it is now, due in some small part to a new following in America. Seattle is home to one of the few broadcasters of classic &quot;Doctor Who&quot; in the world. Find out more about this show, where it started, where it is now, and why it can run for at least another fifty years! Hosted by Eric Gjovaag, (The Emerald City Androgums) Ryan K. Johnson, (Founder, Society of the Rusting TARDIS) and Dan Murphy, (Emerald City Androgums)."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:25PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"STILL TRAVELING IN THE TARDIS: 50 YEARS OF DOCTOR WHO"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join the multi-talented Phil LaMarr as he talks about his work on such shows as Futurama (Hermes Conrad), Justice League (John Stewart), The Avengers: Earth's Mightiest Heroes (Wonder Man) and Star Wars: The Clone Wars (Kit Fisto) as well as his work as the title character on Samurai Jack. Having worked as a voice actor for 30 years, Phil will have a multitude of great stories to share. Come join him for a sure to be entertaining hour! "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:25PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"PHIL LAMARR - MAN OF A 1000 VOICES"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"What time is it? It’s Adventure Time! The top-rated Cartoon Network show and bestselling comic book published by KaBOOM! is bigger than ever in 2013! You won’t want to miss this all-star panel! Join KaBOOM! editor Shannon Watters as she has a lively and fun conversation featuring series writer Ryan North along with series artists Shelli Paroline and Braden Lamb, and writer/artist Natasha Allegri of the new mini-series Fionna and Cake, as they discuss what’s next for the Land of Ooo in the world of comics."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:25PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"IT'S ADVENTURE TIME!"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"If all Ray Park ever did was portray Darth Maul in &quot;Star Wars Episode 1&quot;, this panel would only be amazing. That fact that he's also gone on to portray such geek icons as Toad in the first &quot;X-Men&quot; movie, Chuck Norris in &quot;The Legend of Bruce Lee&quot; and Snake Eyes in both &quot;G.I. Joe&quot; movies only means this panel will be AMAZINGLY AWESOME! Moderated by Mike Jones (Producer, CBS Radio)"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:25PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"RAY PARK - SNAKE EYES SPEAKS!"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join Scott Kurtz (PvP), Kris Straub (Chainsawsuit), Dave Kellett (Sheldon), and Brad Guigar (Evil Inc) for their first live performance of their rollicking podcast in two years! They'll discuss the latest in webcomics, deliver some big news, and end with a lightning-round Q&amp;A."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 8:30PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"WEBCOMICS WEEKLY: ECCC EDITION"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"VISCERA Definition: The large internal organs of the body collectively, particularly those within the abdominal cavity.VISCERA FILM FESTIVAL Definition: Viscera is a non profit organization committed to expanding opportunities for contemporary female horror filmmakers and educating the public by raising awareness of the changing roles for women in the film industry.  Films include Bloodtraffick by Jen Thym,  The Dump by Rebekah McKendry,  The Halloween Kid by Axelle Carolyn,  The Morning After by Jen Moss,  The Night Caller by Donna Thorland and Peter Podgursky,  Sheeties by Paula Haifley,  Mockingbird by Marichelle Daywalt,  Nursery Crimes by Laura Whyte and  Switch by Melanie Light."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 9:30PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"VISCERA FILM FESTIVAL"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 8:30PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"The latter half of 2012 saw the return of two of Dark Horse's classic characters, Ghost and X, new faces like Michael Avon Oeming's The Victories, and Francesco Francavilla's The Black Beetle, and even a completely reimagined hero from yesteryear, Captain Midnight! As we move into 2013, there is no sign of slowing down, as Dark Horse will introduce even more original heroes and villains throughout the year! Join Dark Horse PR Director, Jeremy Atkins, as well as a cast of the industry's top talent, including Kelly Sue DeConnick (Ghost, Captain Marvel, Avengers Assemble), Joe Casey (Catalyst, Sex), Michael Avon Oeming (The Victories, Powers), Francesco Francavilla (The Black Beetle), and Joshua Williamson (Captain Midnight, Masks and Mobsters), for a look at an exciting new cast of characters for 2013!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:05PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"DARK HORSE SUPERHEROES"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:10PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"At DC Entertainment, there’s never been a better time to be a fan!  Come by for unfiltered access on all things DC Entertainment!  Find out what they have to share from behind-the-scenes at your favorite and most talked about Publisher of the past year!  Joining the All-Access party will be some of the industry’s top talents, so don’t miss out! "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:05PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"DC ENTERTAINMENT - ALL ACCESS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:10PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"It's time to talk about sex and violence! Black Kiss II, Butcher Baker, Sex, Saga, Happy!, Multiple Warheads, Sex Criminals: these comics are definitely not for kids. Image Comics creators who aren't shying away from adult situations talk about creating comics for grown-ups. Is there really such a thing as &quot;gratuitous&quot;? What's it like to be banned in the UK and Canada? Join some of comics most respected creators for an eye-opening conversation. Panelists: Joe Casey (Butcher Baker the Righteous Maker, Sex), Howard Chaykin (Black Kiss II), Matt Fraction (Sex Criminals), Fiona Staples (Saga)"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:05PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"PUTTING THE &quot;GRAPHIC&quot; IN GRAPHIC NOVELS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:10PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Are you a writer or artist?  Ever dream of working for Marvel?  Do you find yourself thinking &quot;I could do that if I knew how!&quot;  Well, here's your chance!  Join C.B. Cebulski, Marvel's Talent Scout, and panelists Cullen Bunn (Fearless Defenders), Shawn Crystal (Deadpool), Christos Gage (First X-Men), Joe Keatinge (Morbius), and Matteo Scalera (Secret Avengers) to find out the answers on how to get your foot in the door at MARVEL! "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:05PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"BREAKING INTO COMICS THE MARVEL WAY"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:10PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join Bill Willingham, creator of the multi-Eisner Award winning series Fables and Fairest, Group Editor Shelly Bond and others as they look back on 10+ years of the amazing journey that is Fables, plus an in depth look into what the future holds! Don’t miss this panel that is truly legendary."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 8:40PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"THE OFFICIAL WEST COAST &quot;FABLES&quot; PANEL"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:10PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"What child hasn't dreamed of building with LEGO bricks for a living? Well Mariann Asanuma has been doing it for over 10 years. Mariann's clients have included Google, McDonald's, and Warner Brothers. See how she talks about her time at LEGOLAND California and becoming a freelance LEGO Artist and Author. You can also visit her at http://modelbuildingsecrets.com/"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:15PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"BUILDING WITH LEGO - FOR A LIVING!"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:20PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"The landscape of the comics field has changed since the days of the letter column and the mimeographed fanzine. Now, readers and creators interact with each other through social media, and careers can be built (and sometimes ended?) entirely online. The online realm is not simply a means for promotion of print products or an avenue for digital distribution methods, but is an entirely new ecosystem of interaction, production, and communication. Join panelists Allison Baker, Jen Vaughn, Shannon Watters, Kelly Sue DeConnick, Emi Lenox for a discussion of what works in this new world, what doesn't, and what hasn't been tried yet."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:15PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"THE BIG PICTURE"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:20PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Digital distribution, crowdfunding and cross-platform “transmedia” storytelling are giving fans new ways to enjoy their favorite characters and providing new avenues for creators to reach the audience. Join author/futurist Rob Salkowitz (Comic-Con and the Business of Pop Culture) in conversation with pioneers Mark Waid (Thrillbent), Hank Kanalz (DC Comics), David Steinberger (comiXology), Allison Baker (MonkeyBrain Comics) and Jordan Weisman (gaming/transmedia innovator) to find out what’s next for the art form and the business. "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:15PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"THE FUTURE OF COMICS - WHAT'S AHEAD"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:20PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Most comic book fans have at least heard the name of Jack Kirby, co-creator of such archetypal superheroes as Captain America, The Incredible Hulk, and The Fantastic Four. But comparatively few are aware of the full range and extent of Kirby's achievement. His most famous creations at Marvel represent just ten years out of a career that spanned four decades, and during which Kirby produced Western, War, Crime, Science-Fiction, and Romance comics - making him one of the most prolific and generically wide ranging artists in the history of the art form. Perhaps even fewer fans understand the full extent of Kirby's role in shaping the modern Marvel Universe, or the nature of his working relationship with Stan Lee, or why the issue of creative credit for those great comics is so controversial. Join Professor Charles Hatfield (Cal. State, Northridge) and Professor Ben Saunders (University of Oregon) as they offer an illustrated lecture in which they will survey Kirby's great career; detail the workings of the so-called &quot;Marvel method&quot; for creating comics; demonstrate the ongoing importance of Kirby's legacy; and argue for Kirby's reputation as one of the very greatest American comic-book creators of the 20th century. They will also take questions from the audience. By the end of this discussion, even skeptics will know why they should care about Jack Kirby!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:15PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"WHY YOU SHOULD CARE ABOUT JACK KIRBY"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:20PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"There's nothing sexier than folding, tucking, and pinching... paper into naughty, adult shapes! After an 18+ late-show with comic artist Lar deSouza, you will be able to impress your friends with your new X-Rated folding skills! Let's be honest people, how often are you going to see something like this? A professional illustrator for over 20 years, Lar is the cartoonist for the 2008 Shuster Award winning online comics, &quot;Least I Could Do&quot;, which is updated seven times weekly at www.leasticoulddo.com, and &quot;Looking For Group&quot;, which is updated Mondays and Thursdays at www.lfgcomic.com . Lar has also been the recipient of the Prix Aurora Award for Artistic Achievement in Canadian Science Fiction (2009, 2008, 2006) and numerous other awards for caricature and cartooning."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 8:30PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"HALL"</location>
 <name>"ADULT ORIGAMI"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:20PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"She's been the love interest of a horrible doctor, leads one of the fiercest (and funniest) guilds in all the world (of Warcraft), and holds the honor of being called the &quot;Warrior Queen Goddess of All Nerds&quot; (Gawker) She's Felicia Day! Join her for an hour as she talks about her carreer and let you know what the future holds for the woman Joss Whedon says will someday &quot;rule Asia and invent a new color!&quot; Moderated by Melanie McFarland (TV Editor, IMDB.Com)"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:00PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"MAIN"</location>
 <name>"FELICIA DAY - WARRIOR QUEEN GODDESS OF ALL NERDS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Billy Dee Williams first gained public recognition portraying football player Gale Sayers in &quot;Brian's Song&quot; but it's his role as Lando Calrissian, Han Solo's roguishly suave friend in the original Star Wars trilogy, that gained him millions of fans worldwide. Come hear him talk about those roles as well as his work as an established painter, with some of his work being displayed in such prestigious institutions as The Smithsonian. Moderated by Dave “Softy” Mahler (Sports Radio, KJR 950 AM)"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:00PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"MAIN"</location>
 <name>"HE'S NOT A SYSTEM, HE'S BILLY DEE WILLIAMS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Spend an hour with &quot;The Walking Dead&quot; actors Chandler Riggs and Danai Gurira as they talk about all things undead! Moderated by John Hopperstad (Anchor, Q13 FOX)"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:00PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"MAIN"</location>
 <name>"TALKING DEAD WITH CHANDLER RIGGS AND DANAI GURIRA"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"&quot;Doc&quot; Brown. Uncle Fester. Judge Doom. Jim Ignatowski. These are just some of the iconic roles that  Christopher Lloyd has played. Come hear him talk about his career and his life in this amazing panel moderated by Danny Bonaduce and Sarah ( KZOK,102.5 FM). It will be heavy."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:00PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"MAIN"</location>
 <name>"CHRISTOPHER LLOYD - GENERATING 1.21 GIGAWATTS OF EXCITEMENT!"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Do not miss the panel that everyone was talking about last year! Join Phil LaMarr, Jim Cummings, Richard Horevitz, Grey DeLisle, Quinton Flynn and Kevin Michael Richardson as they bring you the continuing adventures of Luke and the gang in a galaxy far, far away. Guaranteed to bring a smile to your face!"</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 8:45PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"MAIN"</location>
 <name>"STAR WARS - THE VOICE ACTOR SHOW"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Harvey and Shuster Award nominated Kill Shakespeare co-creators Anthony Del Col and Conor McCreery, will walk you through how to write for comics. They'll discuss everything from how to plan your story, the three masks your characters should wear, how to work with an artist to make dynamic page layouts, all the way to the art process (penciling, inking, colouring) and final production elements (lettering)."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 3:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"WORKSHOP"</location>
 <name>"WRITING FOR COMICS"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 3:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Kyle Winters and Mike Andersen used Kickstarter to successfully fund Trigger Men, their first venture in to the world of comics, but the road wasn't easy. At this panel they will discuss what they did right, what they did wrong, and what to do once you're funded. The goal is to give you, the aspiring indie creator, the real knowledge and know how needed to tackle self-publishing with the help of Kickstarter."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 4:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"WORKSHOP"</location>
 <name>"COMICS FROM SCRATCH WITH KICKSTARTER"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 4:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Veteran editor and New York Times best-selling author Philip Athans leads a spirited Q&amp;A for aspiring fantasy and SF writers of all levels. Philip Athans is the New York Times best-selling author of Annihilation and a dozen other books including &quot;The Guide to Writing Fantasy and Science Fiction&quot;, and the recently-released &quot;How to Start Your Own Religion&quot; and &quot;Devils of the Endless Deep&quot;. His blog, Fantasy Author's Handbook, (http://fantasyhandbook.wordpress.com/) is updated every Tuesday, and you can follow him on Twitter @PhilAthans."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 5:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"WORKSHOP"</location>
 <name>"THE GUIDE TO WRITING FANTASY &amp; SCIENCE FICTION"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 5:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Don't sign that contract until you attend this panel! Katie Lane and Caitlin DiMotta, attorneys dedicated to helping creators protect their rights and get paid fairly for the work they do, will show you how to read through (and understand!) your next contract with a publisher, client or collaborator. They'll help make sense of legalese, discuss some of the different ways copyrights can be divvied up in a contract, and talk about some of the pros and cons of work-for-hire jobs. A must attend panel for freelancers and independent artists! Due to time &amp; ethical constraints, the presenters will not be able to provide legal advice about attendees specific legal conundrums during this panel."</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 6:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"WORKSHOP"</location>
 <name>"HOW TO READ AND UNDERSTAND YOUR NEXT PUBLISHING CONTRACT"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 6:00PM" </datetime>
    </Event>
<Event>
<description>"Join Comfort Love and Adam Withers, the three-time Harvey Award nominated creators of the upcoming How-To book, The Complete DIY Guide for Comics Self-Publishing, who will not only talk about how to make a great character, but will create a new character on the spot with the audience's help. The seminar will be broken into two halves: first, Comfort and Adam will take you through the concepts of what it takes to make an awesome character. In the second, they will invite audience participation in creating a new character which will be concepted and drawn on the spot. "</description>
 <end>"3/4/2013 7:55PM"</end>
 <kind>"Panel"</kind>
 <location>"WORKSHOP"</location>
 <name>"LET'S MAKE A CHARACTER!"</name>
 <datetime>"3/4/2013 7:00PM"</datetime> 
</Event>
  </Schedule>
</xml>